[MICROPHONE FEEDBACK]
THE CATEGORY IS:
DANCE OR DIE
[OMINOUS VOCALS]
[CROWD] HA !
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
HA!
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
HA!
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
HA!
♪♪♪
♪ PAY THE TOLL TO THE ANGELS ♪
♪ DRAWING CIRCLES
IN THE CLOUDS ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR MIND
ON THE DISTANCE ♪
♪ WHEN THE DEVIL TURNS AROUND ♪
♪ HOLD ME
IN YOUR HEART TONIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE MAGIC
OF THE DARK MOONLIGHT ♪
♪ SAVE ME
FROM THIS EMPTY FIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE GAME OF LIFE ♪
♪ LIKE A POEM SAID BY A LADY
IN RED ♪
♪ YOU HEAR THE LAST FEW WORDS
OF YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ WITH A HAUNTING DANCE—
NOW YOU’RE BOTH IN A TRANCE ♪
♪ IT’S TIME TO CAST YOUR SPELL
ON THE NIGHT ♪
♪ “ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ AMOR OO NA NA ♪
♪ ABRAC CA DA BRA ♪
♪ MORTA OO GAGA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ ABRA OO NA NA” ♪
♪ IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID ♪
♪ DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT ♪
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ FEEL THE BEAT
UNDER YOUR FEET ♪
♪ THE FLOOR’S ON FIRE ♪
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ CHOOSE THE ROAD ♪
♪ ON THE WEST SIDE ♪
♪ AS THE DUST FLIES ♪
♪ WATCH IT BURN ♪
♪ DON’T WASTE TIME
ON A FEELING ♪
♪ USE YOUR PASSION ♪
♪ NO RETURN ♪
♪ HOLD ME
IN YOUR HEART TONIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE MAGIC
OF THE DARK MOONLIGHT ♪
♪ SAVE ME FROM
THIS EMPTY FIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE GAME OF LIFE ♪
♪ LIKE A POEM SAID BY A LADY
IN RED ♪
♪ YOU HEAR THE LAST FEW WORDS
OF YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ WITH A HAUNTING DANCE—
NOW YOU’RE BOTH IN A TRANCE ♪
♪ IT’S TIME TO CAST YOUR SPELL
ON THE NIGHT ♪
♪ “ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ AMOR OO NA NA ♪
♪ ABRAC CA DA BRA ♪
♪ MORTA OO GAGA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ ABRA OO NA NA” ♪
♪ IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID ♪
♪ DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT ♪
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ FEEL THE BEAT
UNDER YOUR FEET ♪
♪ THE FLOOR’S ON FIRE ♪
♪ ABRA-CA-DABRA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ PHANTOM OF THE DANCE FLOOR ♪
♪ COME TO ME ♪
♪ SING FOR ME A SINFUL MELODY ♪
♪ AH AH AH AH AH ♪
♪ AH AH AH AHH ♪
♪ AHH AH AH AHHHHHH ♪
[CROWD CHANTING] “ABRACADABRA
AMOR OO NA NA
ABRAC CA DA BRA
MORTA OO GAGA
- [LADY GAGA SCREAMS]
- ABRACADABRA
ABRA OO NA NA”
IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID
DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT
♪ “ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ AMOR OO NA NA ♪
♪ ABRAC CA DA BRA ♪
♪ MORTA OO GAGA ♪
♪ ABRACADABRA ♪
♪ ABRA OO NA NA” ♪
♪ IN HER TONGUE SHE SAID ♪
♪ DEATH OR LOVE TONIGHT ♪
[ THUNDERSTORM ]